LE THE HOANG HAI

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Link online portfolio

P 0868 890 658

lethehoanghai@gmail.com

B leminhquang.home.blog

G hoanghailethe

OBJECTIVE

First goal: spending next 5 years to accelerate my knowledge in every aspect of software development and sharpen my technical skills to create awesome Webs/Apps that customers love to use.

Second goal: becoming a senior software engineer. Dedicate my ability and creativity to a professional organization.

EXPERIENCE

2016 - 2017 Work at Atlantic Group as IR Executive

2018 - 2019 Work at Queen Land Real Estate as Sale Executive

2019 - 2020 Work at CEO Group as R&D Executive

Three key roles in previous positions:

- Research new Technology.
- Design Database and analyze data to conduct reports
- Consulting for decision-makers about choices, solutions

MY DEMONSTRATING PROJECTS

- 1. BMI web written in JS vanilla
- 2. Folding card game –JS vanilla
- 3. Todo site JS vanilla
- 4. Battle Ship game Java
- 5. Tic Tac Toe game Java
- 6. Todo app Springboot + React
- 7. CRM web Springboot + Thymeleaf
- 8. Shopping site Springboot + VueJS
- 9. Money convert site Springboot + Thymeleaf

EDUCATION

University: National Economics University

Major: Economics Investment.

Degree: Bachelor.

P. LANGUAGE / FRAME WORK

- HTML / CSS / BOOTSTRAP
- IS / IQUERRY / REACT / VUE
- **JAVA / SPRINGBOOT**
- **SQL**

RELEVANT I.T KNOWLEDGE

- **GIT / GITHUB**
- **MICROSERVICE**
- **RESTFUL API**
- **DOCKER**
- **WORDPRESS**
- **CLOUD COMPUTING**

NON - IT SKILLS

- ENGLISH (~ 7.0 IELTS)
- **RESEARCH**
- **CRITICAL THINKING**
- FINANCE / ACCOUNTING
- **CONTENT MARKETING/ SEO**

COURSE ATTENDING

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

CS50 HARVARD

FREECODECAMP COURSE

REACT CRASH COURSE

MYSOL DATABASE